starter_kits:
  acquia_cms_enterprise_low_code:
    name: "Acquia CMS Enterprise Low-code"
    description: "The low-code starter kit will install Acquia CMS with Site Studio and a UIkit. It provides drag and drop content authoring and low-code site building. An optional content model can be added in the installation process."
    modules:
      require:
        - acquia_cms_site_studio
        - acquia_cms_page
        - acquia_cms_search
        - acquia_cms_tour
        - acquia_cms_toolbar
        - google_tag
        - honeypot
        - mnsami/composer-custom-directory-installer
        - recaptcha
        - reroute_email
        - shield
      install:
        - acquia_cms_site_studio
        - acquia_cms_page
        - acquia_cms_search
        - acquia_cms_tour
        - acquia_cms_toolbar
    themes:
      require:
        - acquia_claro
      install:
        - acquia_claro
      admin: acquia_claro
      default: cohesion_theme
  acquia_cms_community:
    name: "Acquia CMS Community"
    description: "The community starter kit will install Acquia CMS. An optional content model can be added in the installation process."
    modules:
      require:
        - acquia_cms_search
        - acquia_cms_tour
        - acquia_cms_toolbar
        - google_tag
        - honeypot
        - mnsami/composer-custom-directory-installer
        - recaptcha
        - reroute_email
        - shield
      install:
        - acquia_cms_search
        - acquia_cms_tour
        - acquia_cms_toolbar
    themes:
      require:
        - acquia_claro
      install:
        - acquia_claro
      admin: acquia_claro
      default: olivero
  acquia_cms_headless:
    name: "Acquia CMS Headless"
    description: "The headless starter kit preconfigures Drupal for serving structured, RESTful \ncontent to 3rd party content displays such as mobile apps, smart displays and \nfrontend driven websites (e.g. React or Next.js)."
    modules:
      require:
        - acquia_cms_headless
        - acquia_cms_search
        - acquia_cms_tour
        - acquia_cms_toolbar
        - consumer_image_styles
        - mnsami/composer-custom-directory-installer
        - reroute_email
        - shield
      install:
        - acquia_cms_headless_ui
        - acquia_cms_search
        - acquia_cms_tour
        - acquia_cms_toolbar
        - consumer_image_styles
    themes:
      require:
        - acquia_claro
      install:
        - acquia_claro
      admin: acquia_claro
      default: olivero
questions:
  build:
    starter-kit:
      question: "Please choose bundle from one of the above use case"
      default_answer: "acquia_cms_enterprise_low_code"
      answer: "${env.STARTER_KIT}"
    demo-content:
      if: questions["starter-kit"] in ["acquia_cms_enterprise_low_code", "acquia_cms_headless", "acquia_cms_community"]
      question: "Do you want to enable demo content (yes/no) ?"
      allowed_values:
        - yes
        - no
      default_answer: "no"
      answer: "${env.DEMO_CONTENT}"
      class: '\AcquiaCMS\Cli\Helpers\AlterStarterKit::postDemoContent'
    content-model:
      if: questions['starter-kit'] in ["acquia_cms_enterprise_low_code", "acquia_cms_headless", "acquia_cms_community"] && questions['demo-content'] == "no"
      question: "Do you want to enable the content model (yes/no) ?"
      allowed_values:
        - yes
        - no
      default_answer: "no"
      answer: "${env.CONTENT_MODEL}"
      class: '\AcquiaCMS\Cli\Helpers\AlterStarterKit::postContentModel'
    dam-integration:
      if: questions['starter-kit'] in ["acquia_cms_enterprise_low_code", "acquia_cms_headless", "acquia_cms_community"]
      question: "Would you like to enable the Acquia DAM modules (configuration will need to be done manually later after site installation) ?"
      allowed_values:
        - yes
        - no
      default_answer: "no"
      answer: "${env.DAM_INTEGRATION}"
      class: '\AcquiaCMS\Cli\Helpers\AlterStarterKit::postDamQuestion'
    gdpr-integration:
      if: questions['starter-kit'] in ["acquia_cms_enterprise_low_code", "acquia_cms_community"]
      question: "Would you like to add GDPR functionality to the site (Yes/No) ?"
      allowed_values:
        - yes
        - no
      default_answer: "no"
      answer: "${env.GDPR_INTEGRATION}"
      class: '\AcquiaCMS\Cli\Helpers\AlterStarterKit::postGdprQuestion'
  install:
    nextjs-app:
      if: questions['starter-kit'] == "acquia_cms_headless"
      question: "Would you like to preconfigure a next.js site (yes/no) ?"
      allowed_values:
        - yes
        - no
      default_answer: "no"
      answer: "${env.NEXTJS_APP}"
    nextjs-app-site-url:
      if: questions['starter-kit'] == "acquia_cms_headless" && questions['nextjs-app'] == "yes"
      question: "Please provide the Next.js site url"
      default_answer: "http://localhost:3000"
      answer: "${env.NEXTJS_APP_SITE_URL}"
      warning: |-
        The site url is not set. Using default: 'http://localhost:3000'.
        You can set the site url later from: /admin/config/services/next.
    nextjs-app-site-name:
      if: questions['starter-kit'] == "acquia_cms_headless" && questions['nextjs-app'] == "yes"
      question: "Please provide the Site Name"
      default_answer: "Headless Site"
      answer: "${env.NEXTJS_APP_SITE_NAME}"
      warning: |-
        The Site Name is not set. Site Name is set to 'Headless Site'.
        You can set the site url later from: /admin/config/services/next.
    nextjs-app-env-file:
      if: questions['starter-kit'] == "acquia_cms_headless" && questions['nextjs-app'] == "yes"
      question: "Please provide the .env.local file path"
      answer: "${env.NEXTJS_APP_ENV_FILE}"
    gmaps-key:
      if: questions['starter-kit'] in ["acquia_cms_enterprise_low_code", "acquia_cms_headless", "acquia_cms_community"]
      question: "Please provide the Google Maps API Key"
      answer: "${env.GMAPS_KEY}"
      warning: |-
        The Google Maps API key is not set. So, you might see errors, during enable modules step. They are technically harmless, but the maps will not work.
        You can set the key later from: /admin/tour/dashboard and resave your starter content to generate them.
    sitestudio-api-key:
      if: questions['starter-kit'] == "acquia_cms_enterprise_low_code"
      question: "Please provide the Site Studio API Key"
      answer: "${env.SITESTUDIO_API_KEY}"
      warning: |-
        The Site Studio API key is not set. The Site Studio packages won't get imported.
        You can set the key later from: /admin/cohesion/configuration/account-settings to import Site Studio packages.
    sitestudio-org-key:
      if: questions['starter-kit'] == "acquia_cms_enterprise_low_code"
      question: "Please provide the Site Studio Organization Key"
      answer: "${env.SITESTUDIO_ORG_KEY}"
      warning: |-
        The Site Studio Organization key is not set. The Site Studio packages won't get imported.
        You can set the key later from: /admin/cohesion/configuration/account-settings to import Site Studio packages.
